(Amy:)I think we're good.
(Raj:)Okay, well,
thanks for coming by.
(Bert:)You're nice people.
(Penny:)Well, so are you.
In fact, you know what?
(Penny:)We will never
take you for granite.
(Penny:)Did you get that?
Granite?
(Penny:)A little geology joke.
(Bert:)You need to leave.
(Bert:)I'm in love
with both of you now.
(Penny:)Okay.
Bye.
(Raj:)Uh, pull over.
(Bernadette:)What? Why?
Who are you calling?
(Bernadette:)You're gonna rat me out
to Howard, aren't you?
(Bernadette:)You're such a snitch,
no wonder I don't like you.
(Raj:)Whoa, I'm calling
my dad, okay?
(Raj:)He's got experience
dealing with pregnant ladies
(Raj:)because he's an OBGYN.
(Raj:)And experience
with crazy ladies
(Raj:)because of my mom.
(Dr Koothrapalli(on facetime):)Hello, Rajesh.
(Bernadette:)Are you calling
to ask for money?
(Raj:)What? No.
(Dr Koothrapalli(on facetime):)Are you calling to ask
for things
that cost money?
No.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Great. What's up?
(Amy:)This is my friend,
Bernadette.
(Raj:)She's pregnant,
and she's a bit worried,